Privacy Policy

FUNDRISE, LLC

Effective January 8, 2020

Fundrise, LLC (“Fundrise”) provides online tools to assist companies, potential investors, and

others who are interested or involved in the acquisition, development, leasing, management, and

financing of real estate and real estate projects. This privacy policy (our “Privacy Policy”) describes our

data practices regarding Personal Information (defined below). This Privacy Policy applies to Personal

Information collected through our website, located at www.fundrise.com (the “Site”), or through our app

(collectively, the Site and app are the “Services.”) This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal

Information collected by third party websites or apps not operated by Fundrise.

As a financial company, federal law (the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act, or “GLBA”) also

requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your Personal Information. Please see

the GLBA Appendix at the end of this Privacy Policy to learn more about how we treat your

Personal Information under GLBA.

By accessing the Site and/or using our Services, you are consenting to our use of your Personal

Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Further, your access to and use of the Services is

subject to the Fundrise Terms of Use located at https://fundrise.com/website-documents/Terms of

Service.

Information Fundrise Collects About You

Personal Information You Provide

We use the term “Personal Information” to mean any information that could be used to identify

you, including your name, address, email address, birth date, financial information, cell or land-line phone

number, or any combination of information that could be used to identify you.

What Personal Information we collect from you depends on what Services you choose to use and

how you interact with the Site:

Site Visitors. We have structured our Site so that, as a casual site visitor, you may come to our

Site and review selected information about our Services without registering. However, if you wish to

become an Investor, then we require you to provide certain additional Personal Information.

Investors. If you choose to access our Services as an Investor, we require that you complete a

registration form. An Investor is an individual who is over the age of 18 and has completed the registration

process on the Site. Our registration forms will specify the information which you must provide in order

to enjoy the particular features to which you wish to subscribe, which may include such items as (i) name;

(ii) email address; (iii) phone number(s); (iv) mailing address; (v) social security number (for IRS tax

reporting purposes); (vi) bank account number; and (vii) birth date. Our registration forms may additionally

request information that you may, at your option, choose to provide or withhold. To the extent this

additional information constitutes Personal Information, we will treat it in the manner specified in this

Privacy Policy.

We may require each Investor to provide information designed to verify his or her identity. This

information may include (i) information from a successfully completed electronic check transaction, (ii) a

credit report, or (iii) other similar information designed to authenticate and confirm your identity or to

otherwise comply with applicable law.

We also require each Investor to provide certain financial information. For example, we require

that each Investor also provide Internal Revenue Service Form W-9 data, which includes your Social

Security Number (or Taxpayer Identification Number, where applicable). We also require that Investors

provide us with certain account and other payment information, such as information needed to make

payments via ACH, wire, or electronic checks. Our registration process for Investors provides additional

details on the types of payment information needed.

Users also may choose to upload media files such as videos, photos, text, and other content to

the Site to share with Fundrise and other users. When you upload this content, we may also collect

metadata associated with these media files including date, time, location and device information.

Fundrise’s use of such content will be governed by our user-generated terms and conditions which are

provided at the time of collection of such content.

Location Data. We may collect your location information through our mobile applications by

capturing the location (e.g. latitude/longitude) of your mobile device. If you have given the app permission

to access your location, we may collect your device’s location even if you are not using the Service and

store your location history. If you want to opt-out of the collection of your location data, please adjust your

settings in your mobile device to restrict the app’s access to your location data. Geolocation data may be

used to enhance the Services, for example to offer additional functionality and information regarding your

location in connection with the location of Fundrise properties.

Automatically-Collected Information

Even if you do not register for an account on the Site, we may collect certain information

automatically. For example, we may automatically receive and record in our system the following

information:

● your internet protocol (IP) address and location;

● referrer URL;

● the type and version of your web browser;

● device identifiers including mobile advertising identifiers; and

● your operating system.

We also record page views and other general statistical and tracking information. We use this

data to help us administer and operate our Site, to better understand how our users access and interact

with the Site, and for security and monitoring purposes.

We may send email messages that use a “click-through URL” linked to content on our Site. When

you click one of these URLs, you pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web

page. We track this click-through data to help determine interest in particular topics and measure the

effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked, simply do not click text or

graphic links in the email.

How We Use Your Personal Information

We use your Personal Information for the following business purposes:

● to process transactions that you have authorized us to make;

● to facilitate your activities with respect to our Site;

● to contact you regarding administrative issues, such as questions about your specific request,

or otherwise respond to your comments or requests;

● to verify and authenticate your identity, to help us ensure that the individuals who use the

Site and Services are who they claim to be;

● to prevent, detect, mitigate, and investigate fraud, security breaches, and potentially prohibited

or illegal activities, including, for example, activities prohibited by the Anti-Money Laundering

Act;

● to help us operate our Site;

● to deliver notices regarding your account;

● to comply with IRS requirements and for tax reporting purposes;

● to provide you with information, such as notices of investment opportunities via our Site or

updates concerning investments that you have participated in;

● to send you information we believe is relevant to you, such as news, bulletins, marketing

materials, or other information;

● to enforce this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use;

● to conduct user surveys and questionnaires; and

● to comply with applicable law.

We use aggregated information to analyze the effectiveness of our Site, to improve our Services,

and for other similar purposes. In addition, from time to time, we may undertake or commission statistical

and other summary analyses of the general behavior and characteristics of users participating in our

Services and the characteristics of visitors at our Site, and may share aggregated information with third

parties, including advertisers. We may collect aggregated information through features of the software

that support our Services, through cookies, and through other means described in this Privacy Policy.

To enable us to better understand the characteristics of our Investors and/or to provide services

tailored to your needs, we may combine the Personal Information an Investor provides with certain

automatically-collected information that would not otherwise be personally identifiable. If we combine

or link any automatically-collected, non-individually identifiable information with your Personal

Information, the resulting combination will be treated as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy.

How We Share Personal Data

We do not disclose your Personal Information to unaffiliated third parties except as provided in

this Privacy Policy, as follows:

Service Providers. To assist us in running our business and to perform certain services and

functions, we may share your Personal Information with third-party providers of hosting, payment

processing, transfer agent, email communication and customer support services, analytics, marketing,

and advertising service providers (including Google, Facebook, Instagram, Mixpanel, Cybersource,

Adjust, Wells Fargo and Zendesk among others), which companies provide integrated services to us as

part of our product.

For users who choose to link their bank accounts, we use Plaid Technologies, Inc. (“Plaid”) to

facilitate the automatic connection with, and gather required transaction data from, your financial

institution. In particular, as well as facilitating transactions, we use Plaid to prevent overdrafts on your

account and to prevent, detect, and mitigate fraud. By using our joint services, you grant us and Plaid

the right, power, and authority to act on your behalf to access and transmit your personal and financial

information from the relevant financial institution. You agree to your personal and financial information

being transferred, stored, and processed by Plaid in accordance with the Plaid Privacy Policy (located at

https://plaid.com/legal/#privacy-policy).

IRA. We team up with third-party custodians to allow you to invest your IRA funds in diversified

commercial real estate investments. These parties are not affiliated with Fundrise, but act as a directed

custodian for IRAs and other custodial accounts. If you elect to initiate the opening of a self-directed IRA

account with Fundrise, we streamline the enrollment process by sharing certain Personal Information

with these custodians, including but not limited to your name, Social Security number, date of birth, and

contact information. You are not required to invest your IRA funds as a condition of using the Services.

Affiliates. We may share information with our affiliates, meaning an entity that controls, is

controlled by, or is under common control with Fundrise. Our affiliates may use the Personal Information

we share in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy.

For Legal Reasons. We may share your Personal Information to the extent we reasonably

believe we are required to do so by law or to comply with legal or regulatory requirements, or to protect

against fraud, illegal activity, or to otherwise protect Fundrise against liability.

In Connection with a Corporate Transaction. In the event of a transaction or proposed

transaction involving the transfer of substantially all of the assets of Fundrise or one or more of its

businesses to another entity, whether an affiliate or a third party, or in connection with a bankruptcy, we

may share your Personal Information in the diligence process or to otherwise facilitate the transaction,

and with individuals assisting in the transaction or in connection with a bankruptcy. Your Personal

Information may also be one of the transferred assets as part of the transaction or bankruptcy.

For Safety \& Security. We may reveal your Personal Information to third parties, including law

enforcement agencies, in order to protect the safety and security of our users or of any third party.

Cookies, Pixel Tags, and Similar Technologies

A cookie is a small amount of data, often including a unique identifier, which is sent to your

browser from a website and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

We use both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies, as follows:

Session cookies: We use session cookies to improve navigation on our Site and to collect

aggregate statistical information. A session cookie expires when you close your browser. Because these

cookies are strictly necessary to use the Site, you cannot refuse them.

"Persistent" cookies: Persistent cookies are bits of information that are placed on the hard

drive of your computer and can remain for extended periods of time. Persistent cookies also enable us

to provide enhanced, more personal features (such as showing or hiding notifications), and track and

target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Site. The types of persistent cookies

used on the Site are described in more detail below. You may set your browser so that it does not accept

cookies, and you may also use the direct opt-out tools provided by the parties described below. If you do

not enable or if you disable cookies, however, you may not be able to access certain personalized

features of our Services.

We may also use so-called “pixel tags” – small graphic images (also known as “web beacons”

or “single-pixel images”) – to tell us what parts of our website have been visited or to measure the

effectiveness of marketing campaigns on our Site. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s

computer hard drive, pixel tags are embedded invisibly on our Site. Pixel tags inform us whether emails

have been opened, to help ensure that our messages are of interest to our users. We may tie the

information gathered by pixel tags to our users’ Personal Information, in which case it will be subject to

the terms of this Privacy Policy.

In particular, the Site uses:

● Google Analytics, an analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics

uses cookies to help us analyze how users use the Site. The information generated by the cookie

about your use of the Site will be transmitted to, and stored by, Google. Google will use this

information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Site, compiling reports on Site activity

for Site operators and providing other services relating to Site activity and internet usage,

including tracking which pages of our Site you visit so we can optimize your experience with our

Site. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or

where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. We have implemented the

IP anonymization feature in Google Analytics which anonymizes your IP address to protect

individual privacy. You can opt-out from the collection of this information by Google by

downloading and installing a browser plug-in at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. For

more information on Google Analytics privacy practices, read here and, for information on Google

Analytics cookies expiration, read here.

● Mixpanel, an analytics service provided by Mixpanel, Inc. (“Mixpanel”). Mixpanel provides us

aggregated data around usage and web traffic. You can opt out of Mixpanel tracking by visiting:

https://mixpanel.com/optout/. For more information on Mixpanel’s privacy practices, read

https://mixpanel.com/legal/privacy-policy/.

● Third party advertising cookies and pixels, in connection with our marketing programs,

including Google, Facebook, Twitter, Quora, Outbrain, Taboola, Yahoo, Impact Radius, Penny

Hoarder. We do not use such tools for marketing or re-targeting purposes in relation to users

located outside the U.S. You may find more information on what cookies and similar

technologies have been set and how to manage and delete them at http://preferences-

mgr.truste.com in the United States, or at the European Digital Advertising Alliance’s site

http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/ in Europe. For more information on advertising cookies,

please also consult the Network Advertising Initiative’s online resources at

http://www.networkadvertising.org. If you do not want Twitter specifically to show you interest-

based advertising on and off Twitter, you can visit your Twitter settings under Personalization

and data, or visit the Digital Advertising Alliance’s consumer choice tool at optout.aboutads.info.

If you do not want Facebook to show you interest-based advertising, you can visit Facebook

settings under Your Ad Preferences on Facebook.

Feedback, Questionnaires and Surveys.

Our Site allows site visitors and Investors to participate in surveys and questionnaires, which

from time to time we may post on the Site. We also encourage our users to provide feedback to us about

our Site and our Services. You are free to choose whether you participate in these activities. We may

ask that, in addition to providing your responses, you also provide us with your contact information. In

these instances, we use any Personal Information you choose to provide to us in connection with these

activities for the purposes for which you submit the information.

We aggregate information derived from survey and questionnaire information – with your

Personal Information removed – for monitoring or improving the use and appeal of this Site (with no other

obligation to you and, specifically, with no obligation to compensate you for these uses). You are not

obligated to participate in any of these activities.

Links to Other Sites

This privacy statement applies only to Personal Information collected by our Site. Our Site

contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Fundrise. Fundrise is not responsible for

the privacy practices of such other sites, and we encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site

and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects Personal Information.

Data Security

We have put in place commercially-reasonable security systems intended to prevent

unauthorized access to or disclosure of Personal Information, and we take reasonable steps to secure

and safeguard this Personal Information against loss, theft, and unauthorized use, disclosure, or

modification. With that said, there is no such thing as 100% security of the networks, servers, and

databases we operate or that are operated on our behalf. For example, email sent to or from the Site

may not be secure. Before submitting any Personal Information via the Site, please be aware of these

inherent risks and understand that you do so at your own risk.

Data Retention

We keep your Personal Information for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes

described in this Privacy Policy, while we have a legitimate business need to do so in connection with

your account, or as required by law (e.g., for tax, legal, accounting or other purposes), whichever is

longer.

Your Choices

In general, you may browse the Site without providing Personal Information. However, if you

choose not to provide certain Personal Information through our Site, we may not be able to provide

certain services or process certain of your requests. You will not be able to become an Investor or use

all of the features and products that we offer through this Site.

Depending on the functionality associated with the Site feature you are using, you may be able

to update or delete certain of your Personal Information on the Site. Accordingly, at your request, we will

take reasonable steps to remove your Personal Information from our databases. However, please note

that:

● we may not be permitted to delete your Personal Information completely, due to IRS and

regulatory reporting requirements, investments on the platform and the rights thereof, and

data backups and records of deletions;

● if you request deletion of your Personal Information, you may be unable to use certain features

of the Site and any associated Services;

● certain of your Personal Information may remain in our databases following the deletion of

your account; and

● we may not be able to remove de-identified, anonymous, or aggregate data from our databases.

Any deletion requests may be sent to support@fundrise.com.

If you no longer wish to receive marketing emails from us, you can opt out of these

communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link included in those emails, or by contacting us at

support@fundrise.com. Please understand that you will not be allowed to opt-out of transactional

notices or other legal and related notices concerning your relationship to the Site or your account.

Children’s Privacy

Our Site is not directed to children under the age of 18. We do not knowingly seek to collect or

maintain Personal Information or other information from children under the age of 18. We will use

commercially reasonable efforts to delete any Personal Information or other information later determined

to be provided by a child under the age of 18. Use of the Site by children under the age of 18 is not

permitted. If you become aware that a minor has provided Personal Information through our Site, please

email us at support@fundrise.com.

Changes to This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to alter, modify, update, add to, subtract from or otherwise change this

Privacy Policy at any time, which will become effective as of posting on the Site. We encourage you to

periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we collect, use, and share Personal

Information.

Your California Privacy Rights

“Shine the Light” Law

California law permits users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a

year, free of charge, a list of the third parties to whom we have disclosed their Personal Information (if

any) for such third parties’ direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year, as well as the type of

Personal Information disclosed to those parties. However, Fundrise does not share your Personal

Information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

How We Respond to “Do Not Track” Signals

Our Site currently does not respond to “Do Not Track” (DNT) signals and operates as described

in this Privacy Policy whether or not a DNT signal is received. If we do so in the future, we will describe

how we do so in this Privacy Policy.

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of our Site or Services, or

your dealings with our Site or Services, please contact us at:

You may contact us, for any reason, by email as follows:

support@fundrise.com

You may contact us by mail as follows:

FUNDRISE, LLC

11 Dupont Circle NW

9th Floor

Washington, DC 20036

GLBA Privacy Notice

Rev. 01/2020

FACTS WHAT DOES FUNDRISE, LLC ("FUNDRISE") DO

WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

Why? Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers

the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share,

and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.

What? The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with

us. This information can include:

• Social Security number and income

• Investment experience and assets

• Account transactions and checking account information

When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this

notice.

How? All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business.

In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal

information; the reasons Fundrise chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.

Reasons we can share your personal information Does Fundrise

share?

Can you limit this

sharing?

For our everyday business purposes —

such as to process your transactions, maintain

your account(s), respond to court orders and legal

investigations, or report to credit bureaus

Yes No

For our marketing purposes —

to offer our products and services to you

Yes No

For joint marketing with other financial companies No We don't share

For our affliates' everyday business purposes —

information about your transactions and experiences

Yes No

For our affliates' everyday business purposes —

information about your creditworthiness

No We don’t share

For our affiliates to market to you No We don’t share

For nonaffiliates to market to you No We don't share

Questions? Call (202) 584-0550 or go to www.fundrise.com

Page 2

Who we are

Who is providing this notice?

This notice is being provided on behalf of Fundrise, LLC and its affiliated

companies. A list of Fundrise affiliated companies is located at the end

of this document.

What we do

How does Fundrise

protect my personal information?

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use,

we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures

include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.

How does Fundrise

collect my personal information?

We collect your personal information, for example, when you

• Open an account

• Give us your contact information

• Provide account information

• Buy securities from us

• Give us your income information

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit

bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.

Why can't I limit all sharing? Federal law gives you the right to limit only

• sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes—information

about your creditworthiness

• affiliates from using your information to market to you

• sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to

limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.

Definitions

Affiliates Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be

financial and nonfinancial companies.

• Our affiliates include companies with a Fundrise branded name

Nonaffiliates Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be

financial and nonfinancial companies.

• Fundrise does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to

you.

Joint marketing A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that

together market financial products or services to you.

• Fundrise doesn't jointly market.

Other important information

California Residents Only: Under California law, we will not share information we collect about you with

nonaffiliates unless the law allows. For example, we may share information with your consent, to service your

accounts. We will limit sharing among our affiliates to the extent required by California law.

Page 3

Who is providing this notice?

Fundrise, LLC

Fundrise Advisers, LLC

Rise Companies Corp.

Fundrise East Coast Opportunistic REIT

Fundrise Midland Opportunistic REIT

Fundrise West Coast Opportunistic REIT

Fundrise Real Estate Investment Trust

Fundrise Equity REIT

Fundrise For-Sale Housing eFUND - Washington DC, LLC

Fundrise For-Sale Housing eFUND - Los Angeles CA, LLC

Fundrise National For-Sale Housing eFund, LLC

Fundrise Income eREIT II

Fundrise Growth eREIT II

Fundrise Income eREIT III

Fundrise Growth eREIT III

Fundrise Income eREIT 2019

Fundrise Growth eREIT 2019

Fundrise Income eREIT V

Fundrise Growth eREIT V

Fundrise Income eREIT VI

Fundrise Growth eREIT VI

Fundrise Balanced eREIT

Fundrise Opportunity Fund, LP
